[SQL Server Native Client 10.0]Named Pipes Provider: Could not open a
connection to SQL Server [53].
[SQL Server Native Client 10.0]Login timeout expired
[SQL Server Native Client 10.0]A network-related or instance-specific
error has occurred while establishing a connection to SQL Server.
Server is not found or not accessible. Check if instance name is
correct and if SQL Server is configured to allow remote connections.
For more information see SQL Server Books Online.
